Susan Ann McCartney

♥ Bozeman, Montana 🛎 susanmccartney12@gmail.com 🛘 952-715-1038 🛅 in/susan-a-mccartney 📤 susanmccartney.dev/

PERSONAL PROFILE

Skilled software engineer with a Masters degree and two years of experience in Python and Java with exposure to C, PHP, JavaScript, and Go. Familiar with syntax for Angular, React, TypeScript, Vue, and NextJS. Proven success in team collaboration, task delegation, and dependability.

RESEARCH & PUBLICATION

Masters Thesis

A Framework to Assess Bug-Bounty Platforms Based on Potential Attack Vectors · January 2022 - December 2022

McCartney, S. A. (2022). A FRAMEWORK TO ASSESS BUG-BOUNTY PLATFORMS BASED ON POTENTIAL ATTACK VECTORS (Doctoral dissertation, MONTANA STATE UNIVERSITY Bozeman).

- · Implemented an observational case study to identify a detailed relationship between malware types and file extensions.
- · Constructed a framework that determines potential attack vectors based on the lack of restrictions of file attachments for bug reports.

RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE

Graduate Research Assistant

Montana State University - Software Engineering Lab(SEL)

December 2021 - December 2022, Bozeman, MT

- · Conducted a detailed analysis of Mitre's Common Weakness Enumeration (CWE-200 Suite) the exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor.
- $\cdot \ \, \text{Collected information from the National Institute of Standards and Technologies (NIST) on their new project about the Open Security Controls Assessment Language (OSCAL).}$
- \cdot Collaborated with other teammates on the lab's DHS-sponsored research.

Software Engineering Intern

Workiya

May 2021 - August 2021, Bozeman, MT

- $\cdot \ \text{Led the project to automate package version updates using Dependabot across the team's repositories.}$
- · Used Go and AWS services (such as EC2, S3, and Lambda) to complete infrastructure-related improvements.
- · Collaborated with remote teammates to review code and prepare infrastructure improvements.

Web Developer

Montana State University - Allen Yarnell Center for Student Success

September 2020 - December 2021, Bozeman, MT

- · Collaborated with teammates in maintaining the university student activity database using JavaScript, PHP, and HTML
- \cdot Delegated tasks to developers based on programming difficulty and work availability.
- · Paired with other developers to debug and test fixes in a local environment before pushing changes to production.

EDUCATION

Masters of Science in Computer Science

Montana State University · Bozeman, MT · Dec 2022

Bachelor of Arts in Music Education

Montana State University · Bozeman, MT · Dec 2017

INVOLVEMENT

Design Committee Graduate Representative

Montana State University ⋅ School of Computing ⋅ November 2022 - Present

- $\cdot \ \, \text{Collaborates with architects and university staff to design the new computer science building.}$
- $\cdot \ \mathsf{Participates} \ \mathsf{in} \ \mathsf{offsite} \ \mathsf{visits} \ \mathsf{to} \ \mathsf{buildings} \ \mathsf{in} \ \mathsf{Seattle} \ \mathsf{and} \ \mathsf{San} \ \mathsf{Francisco} \ \mathsf{for} \ \mathsf{inspiration} \ \mathsf{on} \ \mathsf{building} \ \mathsf{design}.$
- $\cdot \ \text{Communicates the concerns of the current working and learning environments from a graduate student's perspective.}$

COURSEWORK

Computer Security

Threat Modeling and Common Vulnerability Exploits

Advanced Software Engineering

UML Diagrams, Software Architecture, and Digital Forensics

SKILLS

Programming Skills: Python, Java, C, PHP, Go, JavaScript, HTML Operating Systems: Linux, Microsoft Windows, Mac OS, Android OS